 - Cin 2_1 -
Aramos : Erf...
Banasura : This is... hmm... embarrassing... Could we at least know what you're here for ?
Iou : I'm here for you ! It seems the old chap was right. I don't know what you prepare, but it's definitely evil !
Banasura : Evil..?
‭Iou : I don't know... Nutjobs who attack me..? You doing I don't know what to kill me..?
Aramos : So you didn't understand ? Why do you think we were able to twist reality like that..? We understood, and that's why we are able to do this. We're programmers. And we are in a game. So we use our knowledge to change this world.

 - Cin 2_2 -
Iou : You're completely-- Wait ! What are you doing, now..?
Aramos : Glups...
Iou : What the hell... And what's the deal with this remote ?
Banasura : If you must know... It allows us to...

 - Cin 2_3 -

Banasura : Oomph...
Aramos : Arh...
Iou : A ninja..? I don't know what's going on but... I think I'll take this and let you play, hmm ?

 - Noir -
...

 - Ismael  Iou fenêtre -
Ismael : You're back.
Iou : Surprised ? I must admit you were right.
Ismael : Ah. Tell me what happened.

 - noir -
...

 - Ismael Iou fenêtre - 

Ismael : I see you have encountered the programmers. They told you the truth. They will soon control the world if we don't stop them. I couldn't tell it or you would have driven me out thinking I what a madman. Well done, anywway. So... will you help me ?
Iou : I suppose so... Have I a choice..? And, anyway, I am very frustated because of there last games. It's a pleasure to make them pay.
Ismael : Good ! That is a wise choice. So, your next step is the one they call Aragorn. He is there musician. I marked your map.
Iou : On my way !

 - Ismael Iou  Meryl fenêtre -
Meryl : Wait ! This thing you bringed back ! It'll allow you to make the world bug ! It's... It's wonderful !
Iou : Eh ? You don't seem surprised at all by all this...
Meryl : Let's say I had already made some suppositions... The chair, you know..?
Iou : Ooookay.... And what did you want to tell me about this... Remote ?
Meryl : Here. It's primitive compared to what they used but it'll be useful. Press here to change options and the red button to active it. Simple, eh ?
Iou : And what does it do ?
Meryl : I don't want to break the surprise ! But be careful, though it is powerful, using it too often could... Well I'll pass the technical explanations, but it could destroy the world. So be careful, uh ? *smile*
Iou : Uh...
